<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AICube.FUN</title>
    <link>https://aicube.fun/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AICube.FUN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 06:15:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aicube.fun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Integrate GPT-3 into Google Sheets and Turn Excel Data into Designs</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/w9bvzdhdc6i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 06:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/w9bvzdhdc6i/</guid>
      <description>Overview This post explains how to integrate the AI model GPT-3 into Google Sheets to generate text, and then use Canva to turn spreadsheet data into designs like SWOT analysis templates and event invitations.
Tools Used GPT-3 - Large language model API from Anthropic Google Sheets - Spreadsheet app Canva - Graphic design platform Steps to Integrate GPT-3 into Google Sheets Sign up for an API key at OpenAI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating Social Media Posts with AI</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/mvdtqwfp_pg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 06:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/mvdtqwfp_pg/</guid>
      <description>Social media marketing can be very time consuming, but AI tools offer an excellent way to automate content creation and posting. This allows you to consistently publish high-quality content without spending all your time crafting posts and managing accounts.
Tools Used ChatGPT - Used to generate the text content for posts based on prompts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Amazing AI Tools to 10x Your Coding Productivity</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/4saolpr6bpk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 06:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/4saolpr6bpk/</guid>
      <description>Get ready to have your minds blown by a stellar lineup of coding tools that&amp;rsquo;ll make ChatGPT seem like yesterday&amp;rsquo;s news! I&amp;rsquo;m talking about the ones no one is talking about - and we&amp;rsquo;ll cover them all in 5 minutes.
Tools Perplexity - Gives you Stack Overflow links and articles, and writes code faster than ChatGPT with a beautiful interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use AI to Create 30 Days of Social Media Content in an Hour</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/tlj0m_tddea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 06:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/tlj0m_tddea/</guid>
      <description>Overview This post outlines a step-by-step process for using AI tools to efficiently create a month&amp;rsquo;s worth of social media content in under an hour. The key tools used are:
Jasper - An AI writing assistant that can generate written content on demand Metrical - A social media planning and scheduling tool Canva - A graphic design platform to create images Imgur - An image hosting site to store images By combining these tools, it&amp;rsquo;s possible to quickly produce 30 high-quality social media posts complete with images and text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using ChatGPT to Automate Tinder Messages</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/vm55efbokcm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 06:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/vm55efbokcm/</guid>
      <description>Overview This post describes an experiment using ChatGPT and other AI tools to automate sending customized messages to Tinder matches. The goal was to build an automated system to send engaging opening messages to matches on Tinder.
Tools Used ChatGPT - to generate pickup lines and opening messages OpenAI API - to interface with ChatGPT Selenium - to automate logging in and interacting with the Tinder website Python - to code the bot Implementation Use Selenium to login to Tinder and auto-swipe right to get matches Get match names and profile links using Selenium Feed match names into ChatGPT prompts to generate custom pickup lines Send the messages to matches Results The bot was able to successfully login, get matches, generate messages, and send them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using AI to Efficiently Create Lots of Video Content</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/n60f64u9n_8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 06:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/n60f64u9n_8/</guid>
      <description>AI tools like ChatGPT, InVideo, and AI voiceover can help you quickly and easily create lots of video content. Here&amp;rsquo;s how it works:
Write Scripts with ChatGPT Use ChatGPT to effortlessly write high-quality scripts for your videos. Just give it some prompts about what you want the video to be about, and it will generate an entire script for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using AI to Improve Business Efficiency and Marketing</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/wgdbxnewhra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 05:37:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/wgdbxnewhra/</guid>
      <description>Artificial intelligence (AI) is transforming businesses in many ways, from improving operational efficiency to enhancing marketing efforts. Here are some of the key ways AI can boost business performance:
Streamlining Operations Automating repetitive tasks - AI can take over mundane, repetitive tasks like data entry freeing up employees to focus on more value-adding work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using AI to Automate and Optimize Social Media Marketing</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/pk4fclcdimc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 05:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/pk4fclcdimc/</guid>
      <description>Social media marketing is crucial for modern businesses, but managing multiple platforms and creating engaging content can be extremely time consuming. Thankfully, there are now a variety of AI tools that can help automate and optimize different parts of your social media strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noam Chomsky discusses AI, education, climate change, and vaccines</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/igxzcougvei/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 05:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/igxzcougvei/</guid>
      <description>Tools mentioned: ChatGPT, Google Translate, Live transcription
The renowned philosopher and political activist Noam Chomsky recently participated in an interview covering several important topics:
On AI and education ChatGPT and similar AI systems are just &amp;ldquo;high-tech plagiarism&amp;rdquo; and have no value for real understanding or education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Email Funnels for Online Business</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/1wnf36he88m/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 05:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/1wnf36he88m/</guid>
      <description>Email funnels are a critical part of any online business, especially if you want to generate passive income. However, many people make email funnels more complicated than they need to be. This post aims to simplify email funnels so you can understand the key elements needed to make them profitable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a Profitable Pinterest Brand Step-by-Step</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/annsf5qgff8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 05:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/annsf5qgff8/</guid>
      <description>Overview This post outlines the step-by-step process for building a profitable Pinterest brand from scratch. It covers generating ebook content with GPT-3, designing graphics and covers in Canva/Photoshop, setting up the online store with WAP, building the landing page in Typeform, setting up Pinterest ads, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Set Up the Perfect Remote Work Desk as a Software Engineer</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/tzbqfkspv_m/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 05:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/tzbqfkspv_m/</guid>
      <description>Working remotely as a software engineer can be an amazing experience. You get flexibility, freedom, and the ability to work from anywhere. However, having the right desk setup is crucial for productivity and comfort. Here are my tips for creating the perfect remote work desk as a software engineer:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use ChatGPT and Zapier to Automate Content Creation</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/rkbcy8jqzzg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 05:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/rkbcy8jqzzg/</guid>
      <description>Introduction ChatGPT and Zapier are powerful tools that can be used together to automate content creation and publishing. In this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to use these tools to analyze a YouTube video, generate tweets from it, and automatically publish them to Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Made an Entire Video Game Using Only AI-Generated Code</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/l6vw0um5xtg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 05:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/l6vw0um5xtg/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Recently, I discovered an amazing AI chatbot called ChatGPT that can generate code upon request. I was fascinated by its capabilities, so I decided to put it to the test by having it create an entire simple 2D video game for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review and Rank the Top ChatGPT Plugins</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/cczrjjn7p7u/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 05:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/cczrjjn7p7u/</guid>
      <description>ChatGPT plugins are exploding in popularity, with new ones coming out every day. With so many options, it can be hard to know which plugins are worth your time. In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through a process for reviewing and ranking ChatGPT plugins, so you can find the hidden gems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use ChatGPT to Automate Your Instagram and Grow Your Followers</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/mcvfw9rb3sq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 05:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/mcvfw9rb3sq/</guid>
      <description>Social media can be time consuming to manage. But AI tools like ChatGPT make it easy to automate content creation and posting. In this guide, I&amp;rsquo;ll show you how I used ChatGPT and other AI tools to automatically generate and post content to Instagram daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some creative works related to TwitterX</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/some-creative-works-related-to-twitterx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 23:49:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/some-creative-works-related-to-twitterx/</guid>
      <description>#TwitterX is a trending topic that refers to the rebranding of Twitter as X by its owner Elon Musk. The new logo features a blue X with a scratch mark on it, which has been compared to the logo of an independent music artist named Kxlider³.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ways to get the latest hot topic on twitter</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/ways-to-get-the-latest-hot-topic-on-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 23:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/ways-to-get-the-latest-hot-topic-on-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Bing: There are different ways to get the latest hot topic on twitter.com, depending on your device and preferences. Here are some methods you can try:
Using a computer: You can login to Twitter and open the Explore tab by clicking on the # Explore option or using this link: www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can LLAMA2 be a game changer?</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/can-llama2-be-a-game-changer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 21:40:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/can-llama2-be-a-game-changer/</guid>
      <description>Bing: Llama 2 is an open-source large language model developed by Meta and Microsoft. It is engineered to power a variety of cutting-edge applications including, but not limited to, OpenAI’s ChatGPT and Bing Chat¹. Llama 2 is designed to enable developers and organizations to build generative AI-powered tools and experiences¹.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Promo a product on Meta Threads</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/how-to-promote-a-product-on-meta-threads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 21:00:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/how-to-promote-a-product-on-meta-threads/</guid>
      <description>Bing: Meta has been advising creators on what content they should post on Threads. The social network reportedly provided extensive guidelines on how marketers can integrate their brands on the platform in a leaked email. The message allegedly provided creators with content suggestions, engagement ideas, feature recommendations and specific examples of what makes a good post for inspiration¹.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ways to earn money with AI in 2023</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/ways-to-earn-money-with-ai-in-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 20:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/ways-to-earn-money-with-ai-in-2023/</guid>
      <description>Bing: There are many ways to earn money with AI in 2023, and the specific approach you take will depend on your skills, interests, and resources. Here are a few potential options:
Develop and sell AI-powered products or services: One way to earn money with AI is to create and sell products or services that use AI technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 AI tools that can help you create Twitter content</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/5-ai-tools-that-can-help-you-create-twitter-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 18:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/5-ai-tools-that-can-help-you-create-twitter-content/</guid>
      <description>Bing: There are AI-powered content creation tools that can help you generate Twitter content. These tools can&amp;rsquo;t replace great writers, but they can help writers and marketers save time and use their skills for more strategic aspects of content creation. You can use these tools to generate tweet copy, develop catchy Twitter handles, and find trending topics to share on your Twitter account.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
