<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thoughts on AICube.FUN</title>
    <link>https://aicube.fun/category/thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thoughts on AICube.FUN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 02:01:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aicube.fun/category/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gain Control of Your Free Time</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/post/n3knlfmxslo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 02:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/post/n3knlfmxslo/</guid>
      <description>Speaker: Laura Vanderkam
Summary:
We don&amp;rsquo;t build the lives we want by saving time. We build the lives we want, and then time saves itself. Time is highly elastic - it stretches to accommodate what we choose to put into it. Instead of saying &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t have time&amp;rdquo;, say &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s not a priority&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Editing Your Life Story</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/post/o_mqr4lhm0c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 02:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/post/o_mqr4lhm0c/</guid>
      <description>Key Ideas We are all unreliable narrators of our own lives. The stories we tell ourselves shape our realities.
Most of our stories revolve around two themes - freedom and change. We often feel trapped by circumstances, but we have more freedom than we realize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Al Gore on the Obstacles to Solving the Climate Crisis</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/post/xgzc6da4mco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 01:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/post/xgzc6da4mco/</guid>
      <description>In his TED talk, former US Vice President Al Gore discusses the obstacles to solving the climate crisis and speeding up solutions. He focuses on two main obstacles - the unrelenting opposition from the fossil fuel industry and the global financial system and subsidies for fossil fuels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build Confidence in Yourself and Others</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/post/b5zespoaolu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 01:39:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/post/b5zespoaolu/</guid>
      <description>Brittany Packnett Cunningham gave a thoughtful talk on the importance of building confidence, and how it can empower people to achieve their dreams and change the world. She shared personal stories and insights on how permission, community, and curiosity are key to developing confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Intriguing Differences Between Extroverts and Introverts</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/post/qyvxk_bqlbk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 01:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/post/qyvxk_bqlbk/</guid>
      <description>In his TED talk, psychologist Brian Little discusses some fascinating differences between extroverts and introverts. He explores how our personality traits, especially extroversion vs introversion, affect various aspects of our lives.
Key Points Extroverts need more external stimulation and tend to be more sociable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Speaking the Truth</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/post/qijh4uaqgd8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 01:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/post/qijh4uaqgd8/</guid>
      <description>Speaker: Luvvie Ajayi Jones
Luvvie describes herself as a professional troublemaker. Her purpose is to critique the world and challenge people and systems to do better.
On Fear Luvvie wanted to be a doctor but struggled with chemistry in college. This led her to start blogging in 2003 instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A 3-Step Guide to Believing in Yourself</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/post/zy2zj8yie6c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 01:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/post/zy2zj8yie6c/</guid>
      <description>At a recent TED talk, Emmy-award winning actress Sheryl Lee Ralph shared a 3-step process for believing in yourself even during challenging times.
Background Ralph opened her talk by singing an uplifting song she had performed after winning an Emmy for her role on Abbott Elementary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover Your Authentic Self</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/post/7vqnazqmceq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 01:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/post/7vqnazqmceq/</guid>
      <description>By Beverly Bond at TEDWomen 2019 Bev Bond shared her journey of self-discovery to find her authentic self after years of suppressing her true identity.
Key Takeaways Don&amp;rsquo;t settle - make every day a great adventure even if it&amp;rsquo;s scary sometimes. Bond quit her fashion job at 38 to pursue her passion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
