<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thoughts on AICube.FUN</title>
    <link>https://aicube.fun/category/thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thoughts on AICube.FUN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:24:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aicube.fun/category/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sustainable Ways to Cool Homes Without Relying on Air Conditioning</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/post/skbeomcsqai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/post/skbeomcsqai/</guid>
      <description>With rising temperatures due to climate change, cooling our homes is becoming more challenging without exacerbating global warming. Traditional air conditioning consumes massive amounts of energy and emits greenhouse gases, creating a vicious loop of generating more heat. However, there are sustainable solutions using both traditional and modern techniques that don&amp;rsquo;t require as much energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Beauty of Building With Mud, Trash, and Other Sustainable Materials</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/post/eume_9qkxi8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/post/eume_9qkxi8/</guid>
      <description>The construction industry accounts for 30-40% of the world&amp;rsquo;s total energy use and carbon emissions. Architect Vinu Daniel argues we can build more sustainably by using local, natural materials like mud and incorporating waste materials into construction.
Tools and Techniques Mud bricks - Compressed mud bricks with 5% cement can be stronger than fired bricks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Leave Your Past Behind And Move Forward</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/post/xy5o2shsmjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/post/xy5o2shsmjs/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this video conversation between Dr. Rangan Chatterjee and psychotherapist Julia Samuel, they discuss practical ways to move on from past traumas and experiences. Julia shares insights from her work with families and multi-generational trauma.
Key Ideas Trauma and difficult experiences can get passed down through generations, even if you didn&amp;rsquo;t directly experience them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The LONGEVITY Doctor: You SHOULD Be Aware Of This If You CARE About Your Health | Dr. Peter Attia</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/post/obpp0d6m7lu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 15:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/post/obpp0d6m7lu/</guid>
      <description>Key Insights from Dr. Peter Attia on Health and Longevity On the Motivation for Improving Health When confronting mortality, people would give anything for more chance at life. Major life events like having kids often provide the motivation needed to improve health. On Emotional Health Physical health problems can exacerbate emotional health issues.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
