<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on AICube.FUN</title>
    <link>https://aicube.fun/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on AICube.FUN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 09:11:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aicube.fun/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automating Machine Learning Pipelines with GPT Engineer</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/gwy-pj2ofem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 09:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/gwy-pj2ofem/</guid>
      <description>GPT Engineer is a new tool that allows automating the creation of machine learning pipelines by leveraging the power of large language models like GPT-3. It interacts via conversational prompts and clarifying questions to generate full code solutions split across modular files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using ChatGPT to Automate Tinder Messages</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/vm55efbokcm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 06:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/vm55efbokcm/</guid>
      <description>Overview This post describes an experiment using ChatGPT and other AI tools to automate sending customized messages to Tinder matches. The goal was to build an automated system to send engaging opening messages to matches on Tinder.
Tools Used ChatGPT - to generate pickup lines and opening messages OpenAI API - to interface with ChatGPT Selenium - to automate logging in and interacting with the Tinder website Python - to code the bot Implementation Use Selenium to login to Tinder and auto-swipe right to get matches Get match names and profile links using Selenium Feed match names into ChatGPT prompts to generate custom pickup lines Send the messages to matches Results The bot was able to successfully login, get matches, generate messages, and send them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
