<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stable Diffusion on AICube.FUN</title>
    <link>https://aicube.fun/tags/stable-diffusion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stable Diffusion on AICube.FUN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 04:25:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aicube.fun/tags/stable-diffusion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Idea to Clone Interiorai. com with Stable Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/post/clone-interiorai.com-with-stable-diffusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 04:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/post/clone-interiorai.com-with-stable-diffusion/</guid>
      <description>First, you need to prepare a dataset of images and captions that describe the interior design styles and features. You can use existing datasets such as the InteriorNet³ or the LSUN Scene Layout⁴, or you can create your own by scraping images from the web or taking photos of real spaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Idea to Clone Photoai.com with Stable Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/post/clone-photoai.com-with-stable-diffusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 04:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/post/clone-photoai.com-with-stable-diffusion/</guid>
      <description>Cloning photoai.com with Stable Diffusion is a complex task, as photoai.com is a website that offers various packs of photos generated by artificial intelligence. Each pack has a different theme, such as LinkedIn, Tinder, Fantasy-Avatar, Polaroid, etc. The website claims to use a proprietary AI model that can create realistic and diverse photos from a set of 15 or more photos uploaded by the user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversation on the Evolution and Ethics of AI</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/post/_b__l_olcws/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 16:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/post/_b__l_olcws/</guid>
      <description>Overview This is a summary of a conversation between AI experts including Imad Mushtaq, Alexander Wang, and Andrew Ng on the rapid advancement of AI technology and the ethical implications. Key topics discussed:
How AI will transform industries and jobs extremely quickly. Education and reskilling will be critical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Face Swapping in Stable Diffusion using Roop</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/post/m-vd0l6w9fg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 09:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/post/m-vd0l6w9fg/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Roop is a new extension for swapping faces in images generated with Stable Diffusion. It allows you to easily replace a face in an image with a different face from another image.
Installation Installing Roop in Stable Diffusion is very easy. Just go to the Extensions tab in the UI, click on &amp;ldquo;Load from URL&amp;rdquo; under the Available section, and install the Roop extension from the SD Web UI Extensions group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Face Swapping in Images using Automatic1111</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/post/potksdm-fzu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 08:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/post/potksdm-fzu/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Face swapping is the process of replacing a face in an image with a different face, while maintaining the original facial expression and head position. This can be done using AI tools like Stable Diffusion and Automatic1111. In this post, we will discuss how to use Automatic1111 and its Roop extension to easily swap faces in images.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
