<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>marketing on AICube.FUN</title>
    <link>https://aicube.fun/category/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in marketing on AICube.FUN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 02:27:30 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aicube.fun/category/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Open House Strategy to 10x Your Real Estate Business</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/the-ultimate-open-house-strategy-to-10x-your-real-estate-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 02:27:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/the-ultimate-open-house-strategy-to-10x-your-real-estate-business/</guid>
      <description>The Ultimate Open House Strategy to 10x Your Real Estate Business Open houses can be a great way to generate new leads and clients for your real estate business. However, many agents don&amp;rsquo;t have an effective strategy and end up wasting time at open houses without seeing results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Broker vs eXp Realty - The Truth About Compensation &amp; Revenue Share</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/real-broker-vs-exp-realty-the-truth-about-compensation-revenue-share/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 02:26:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/real-broker-vs-exp-realty-the-truth-about-compensation-revenue-share/</guid>
      <description>Real Broker vs eXp Realty - The Truth About Compensation &amp;amp; Revenue Share Overview This post provides an in-depth comparison of the compensation structures and revenue share models of Real Broker and eXp Realty. It analyzes the pros and cons of each brokerage and looks at long-term implications for agents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Create 30 Pieces of Content in 24 Hours Using AI</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/how-to-create-30-pieces-of-content-in-24-hours-using-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 02:25:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/how-to-create-30-pieces-of-content-in-24-hours-using-ai/</guid>
      <description>How to Create 30 Pieces of Content in 24 Hours Using AI We&amp;rsquo;ve almost all interacted with AI in some form, whether using it to create content or just consuming AI-based content. This means the bar for content quality has been raised. However, if we utilize AI tools to assist our content creation process, we can not only be successful in our business but also create pieces of work we wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be capable of before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Create Instagram Reels in 2023 - Step-by-Step Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/how-to-create-instagram-reels-in-2023-step-by-step-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 02:23:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/how-to-create-instagram-reels-in-2023-step-by-step-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>How to Create Instagram Reels in 2023 - Step-by-Step Tutorial Instagram Reels continue to be one of the best ways to reach new audiences and grow your following in 2023. In this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through how to use the Reels editor in the Instagram app to create amazing Reels from start to finish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Gained 30k Instagram Followers with Reels</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/how-i-gained-30k-instagram-followers-with-reels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 02:22:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/how-i-gained-30k-instagram-followers-with-reels/</guid>
      <description>How I Gained 30k Instagram Followers with Reels Over the past few months, I&amp;rsquo;ve grown my Instagram following from 35k to over 66k, and it&amp;rsquo;s all thanks to Reels.
Unlike what most Instagram tips videos recommend, I don&amp;rsquo;t rely on trending audios, hashtags, or posting times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Break 6 Figures in Your First Year as a Real Estate Agent</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/how-to-break-6-figures-in-your-first-year-as-a-real-estate-agent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 02:21:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/how-to-break-6-figures-in-your-first-year-as-a-real-estate-agent/</guid>
      <description>How to Break 6 Figures in Your First Year as a Real Estate Agent Here are the top 10 things to do as a new real estate agent to break 6 figures in your first year:
Create a personal brand and stand out from other agents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Instagram Algorithm Updates and Leaked Projects for 2023</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/top-10-instagram-algorithm-updates-and-leaked-projects-for-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 02:20:39 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/top-10-instagram-algorithm-updates-and-leaked-projects-for-2023/</guid>
      <description>Top 10 Instagram Algorithm Updates and Leaked Projects for 2023 Instagram is constantly evolving with new features and algorithm updates. As a social media manager, it can be difficult to keep up with all the changes. In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll overview the top 10 most important Instagram updates so far in 2023, including some leaked projects that haven&amp;rsquo;t been officially announced yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Start a YouTube Channel as a Real Estate Agent in 2023</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/how-to-start-a-youtube-channel-as-a-real-estate-agent-in-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 02:19:24 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/how-to-start-a-youtube-channel-as-a-real-estate-agent-in-2023/</guid>
      <description>How to Start a YouTube Channel as a Real Estate Agent in 2023 YouTube can be an incredibly powerful platform for real estate agents looking to grow their business and attract new clients. In this blog post, I&amp;rsquo;ll share my top tips on how agents can start their own YouTube channel from scratch and leverage it to generate leads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Use ChatGPT to Create a Complete TikTok Strategy for Real Estate Agents</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/how-to-use-chatgpt-to-create-a-complete-tiktok-strategy-for-real-estate-agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 02:18:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/how-to-use-chatgpt-to-create-a-complete-tiktok-strategy-for-real-estate-agents/</guid>
      <description>How to Use ChatGPT to Create a Complete TikTok Strategy for Real Estate Agents Artificial intelligence (AI) has taken the real estate industry by storm. But ultimately, people don&amp;rsquo;t really know how to properly leverage it.
I know from experience that many real estate agents struggle when it comes to content strategy, especially for TikTok.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Mike Gerard Built a Real Estate Empire Through Youtube Despite Early Criticism</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/how-mike-gerard-built-a-real-estate-empire-through-youtube-despite-early-criticism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 02:17:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/how-mike-gerard-built-a-real-estate-empire-through-youtube-despite-early-criticism/</guid>
      <description>How Mike Gerard Built a Real Estate Empire Through Youtube Despite Early Criticism Mike Gerard is a top real estate agent from Calgary, Canada who has built a massive organization and brand through YouTube, despite facing criticism and self-doubt early on.
In his inspiring presentation, Mike shared how he started creating real estate videos on YouTube five years ago, even though he was insecure, overweight, and inexperienced on camera.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Generate 20&#43; Real Estate Leads from a Single Facebook Ad</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/how-to-generate-20&#43;-real-estate-leads-from-a-single-facebook-ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 02:16:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/how-to-generate-20&#43;-real-estate-leads-from-a-single-facebook-ad/</guid>
      <description>How to Generate 20+ Real Estate Leads from a Single Facebook Ad Facebook ads can be an incredibly powerful way to generate leads for your real estate business if done correctly. In this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through step-by-step how to create a highly targeted Facebook ad campaign that can result in over 20 closed deals from a single ad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How a New Real Estate Agent Used Social Media to Build Massive Momentum and Close Over $80k in Commissions</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/how-a-new-real-estate-agent-used-social-media-to-build-massive-momentum-and-close-over-80k-in-commissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 02:14:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/how-a-new-real-estate-agent-used-social-media-to-build-massive-momentum-and-close-over-80k-in-commissions/</guid>
      <description>How a New Real Estate Agent Used Social Media to Build Massive Momentum and Close Over $80k in Commissions Real estate can be an incredibly lucrative business, but it&amp;rsquo;s notoriously difficult for new agents to build momentum and start closing deals, especially in their first few months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some creative works related to TwitterX</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/some-creative-works-related-to-twitterx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 23:49:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/some-creative-works-related-to-twitterx/</guid>
      <description>#TwitterX is a trending topic that refers to the rebranding of Twitter as X by its owner Elon Musk. The new logo features a blue X with a scratch mark on it, which has been compared to the logo of an independent music artist named Kxlider³.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ways to get the latest hot topic on twitter</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/ways-to-get-the-latest-hot-topic-on-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 23:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/ways-to-get-the-latest-hot-topic-on-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Bing: There are different ways to get the latest hot topic on twitter.com, depending on your device and preferences. Here are some methods you can try:
Using a computer: You can login to Twitter and open the Explore tab by clicking on the # Explore option or using this link: www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 AI tools that can help you create Twitter content</title>
      <link>https://aicube.fun/5-ai-tools-that-can-help-you-create-twitter-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 18:52:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aicube.fun/5-ai-tools-that-can-help-you-create-twitter-content/</guid>
      <description>Bing: There are AI-powered content creation tools that can help you generate Twitter content. These tools can&amp;rsquo;t replace great writers, but they can help writers and marketers save time and use their skills for more strategic aspects of content creation. You can use these tools to generate tweet copy, develop catchy Twitter handles, and find trending topics to share on your Twitter account.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
